Guide to The Adrian Flannelly Show Audio Recordings AIA.089
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- The Adrian Flannelly Show, 1978-2000; 256 audiocassettes in 4 flatboxes and 2 record cartons
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 September 23 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0240)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 September 30 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0241)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 October 7 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0242)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 October 14 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0243)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 October 28 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0244)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 November 4 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0245)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #1, 2000 November 11 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0246)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #2, 2000 November 11 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0247)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #1, 2000 November 18 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0248)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows - WLUX #2, 2000 November 18 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0249)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 November 25 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0250)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 December 2 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0251)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 December 9 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0252)
  - Adrian Flannelly Irish Radio Shows, 2000 December 16 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0253)
  - A. Flannelly/B. Maxwell (22'), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0254)
  - A. Flannelly/J. Roach (A.O.H.), undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0255)
  - Adrian Flannelly Interview, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0256)
- Additional Tapes, 1976-2001; 71 audiocassettes in 1 flat box and 2 record cartons
  This series contains 71 audiocassettes donated by Flannelly whose association with his radio program is unclear.
  - Ireland Xmas - Fintans House, 1976 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0257)
  - No Guests, 1977 November (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0258)
  - Easter Sunday, Irish Ballet & Frank Durkin, 1979 April 15 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0259)
  - Christmas Greeting, 1981 December 20 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0260)
  - Vlichy Carter, 1983 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0261)
  - PFB, 1983 August 15 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0262)
  - Sound Check - Trish, 1983 March (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0263)
  - Ballyohoneen, 1984 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0264)
  - No Guests, 1984 July (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0265)
  - Dermot O'Brien (Great Irish Fair), 1985 September (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0266)
  - APF, 1985 October 12 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0267)
  - Guss Hayes, 1986 January (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0268)
  - Irish Ambassador Padriac McKiernan, Hal Roach, 1986 January/February? (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0269)
  - Malachy-Brendan Shine, 1986 February (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0270)
  - Malachy-Frank Patterson, Suzanne Stein, 1986 February (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0271)
  - Aircheck, 1986 March 9 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0272)
  - Dearie - Pat McGuigan-Jimmy Kelly-Malachy, 1986 May (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0273)
  - Malachy, 1986 May (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0274)
  - Untitled, 1986 May 25 (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0275)
  - Trish - Cadrian in Ireland, Frank Noland/Mattie Connolly, 1986 July (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0276)
  - Stockton Wing. Peter Barry, 1986 September (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0277)
  - Jim Flavin - Lottery - Visas, Eamon Doran, 1986 December (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0278)
  - Freddy White, Paddy Noonan, Noel Kingston, Ed McKenna - Irish Center, 1986 December 6 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0279)
  - Maureen O'Hara, 1987 January (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0280)
  - Flavin.Visas.Ray Collins, 1987 February (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0281)
  - Charles Haughey Interview, 1988 April 20 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0282)
  - Liveline, 1988 May 27, 1988 May 30 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0283)
  - Gay McIntyre, 1988 October 30 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0284)
  - Untitled, 1989 January (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0285)
  - St. Patrick's Day, 2000 March 17 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0286)
  - Untitled, 2000 October 21 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0287)
  - 1:20, 2000 December 30 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0288)
  - 1:20 #2, 2000 December 30 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0289)
  - :60 #3, 2000 December 30 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0290)
  - Untitled #1, 2001 January 6 (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0291)
  - Untitled #2, 2001 January 6 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0292)
  - Untitled #3, 2001 January 6 (Box 6, Audiocassette 089.0293)
  - Adrian on Local Radio - Ballina, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0294)
  - Barry Moore, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0295)
  - Brian Murphy, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0296)
  - Catholic Charities PSAs 60-50-30, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0297)
  - Christy Moore, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0298)
  - Dukakis lined up for Adrian, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0299)
  - Excerpt Mayor of Derry, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0300)
  - Extract from MWR + NWR "The Rambling House", undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0301)
  - Gay Byrne Show, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0302)
  - Glen Miller/G. Gershwin/L. Ronstat, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0303)
  - Haughey, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0304)
  - Haughey Dimaur NY, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0305)
  - J Bastable/ An Hengas, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0306)
  - Kennedy Hearings, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0307)
  - Noon, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0308)
  - Old Flames R.I.P., undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0309)
  - Prime Minister Ireland/Garret Fitzgerald, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0310)
  - Ruthie Morrissey - Irish Soldier Boys, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0311)
  - Simple Mix Gold Dream, undated (Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0312)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Audiocassette 089.0313 - 089.0314, Box 4, Audiocassette 089.0315 - 089.0327)